Guide to the Donohoe Kelly & Co. Records, 1863-1917 JL002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Donohoe Kelly & Co. Records,
1863-1917
JL002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
84.0 Linear feet
Donohoe Kelly & Co.
Materials withdrawn from the collection
Duplicates; cancelled checks; statements from various banks (recorded in statement books); deposit slips (sampled); telegram memos (sampled); account envelopes (sampled); clearing house proofs, checks, memos (sampled).
Scope and Content
The collection consists of a relatively small percentage of loose material and a much larger percentage of bound volumes.
The loose material includes a variety of general business papers. Of particular interest are those dealing with Donohoe, Ralston and Company in Liquidation, which cover a four year period (1863-1867) of evaluation and recapitulation of the old company. Much of the other material consists of correspondence, notes, etc. to the bank regarding individual and company accounts. This is quite routine business, but presents an interesting cross section of the way routine affairs were conducted in banking sixty and seventy years ago.
Letters of credit, insurance policies, and business papers relating to income tax, semi-annual reports, balance sheets and statements comprise the remainder of the loose material.
The volumes include either complete or near-complete series of general cash books, blotters, checks and deposits volumes, draft stubs, collection journals, and balance sheets in bound groups, as well as statements and remittance records from other banks.
General ledger vouchers, for which there are no ledgers, are included at the end of the collection, and are left in their original bundles, arranged chronologically by month and year.
The records of the Donohoe, Kelly Banking Company certainly will be of interest to anyone with a desire to know a lot about banking practices in the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries
Historical Note
The Donohoe, Kelly Banking Company was a large private banking company formed in the second half of the nineteenth century, and flourishing until 1929 when it transferred its business to the Bank of America of California, later the Bank of America, National Trust and Savings Association. The company was established in 1861 by Joseph A. Donohoe, Eugene Kelly and W.C. Ralston as Donohoe, Ralston and Company, and Eugene Kelly and Company was later organized to represent the company in the East.
In 1864 Ralston left the company and subsequently was instrumental in establishing the Bank of California, while Donohoe, Ralston and Company became Donohoe, Kelly and Company in the same year. John W. Flood and Howard Havens joined Donohoe and Kelly in 1876 with no alteration in the title. In 1891 this private banking firm was incorporated under the State laws of California as the Donohoe, Kelly Banking Company and remained so until 1929.
Provenance
Gift of Joseph A. Donohoe, Jr. to the Jackson Library of Business in 1951. Transferred to the Department of Special Collections in 1979.
Access Restrictions
None.
- Series A. General Business Papers, Correspondence, (1863-1914) (Box 1-17)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of loose material arranged in several different patterns within the series. The material is dated from 1863 to 1914 and consists of letters regarding individual and company accounts, letters of credit, insurance policies, and financial business papers.
  - DONOHOE, RALSTON AND COMPANY IN LIQUIDATION in chronological order., (1863-1867) (Box (1))
  - ACCOUNTS in alphabetical order., (1865-1911) (Box (5-10))
  - LETTERS OF CREDIT in number series., (1899-1912) (Box (11))
  - INSURANCE POLICIES in alphabetical order by insurance company., (1881-1911) (Box (12))
  - FINANCIAL BUSINESS PAPERS by groups of document type., (1863-1912) (Box (13-15))
  - CHECK SAMPLES, ACCOUNT SAMPLES, (1908-1914) (Box (16-17))
- Series B. General Account Books, (1864-1919) (Volume 18-830)
  These volumes contain the bulk of the material in the collection, including daybooks, blotters, cash books, checks and deposits records, collection books, remittance books, draft stubs, checkbooks, balance sheets and collection letter books. They are arranged by record type groups and chronologically.
- Series C. General Ledger Vouchers, (1906-1917) (Volume 831-838)
  The vouchers are tied in bundles and kept in boxes in a chronological arrangement by month and year.
- Series A. General Business Papers, Correspondence
  - DONOHOE, RALSTON & COMPANY IN LIQUIDATION
    - Financial statements, 1863-June 1864 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Financial statements, July 1864-October 1864 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Financial statements, November 1864-1867 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Stock Journal-Donohoe-Kelly & Co.-, 1892-1909 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACCOUNTS
    - Abrahm and Karsky Co., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - N. Abrams, 1892
    - N. Ahrens, 1903-1905
    - The Alden Co., 1910
    - Alturas Quartz Mine, 1868-1871
    - T. Ambrose, 1883
    - American Exchange in Europe, 1882
    - H. Amy & Co., 1866
    - I.P. Anderson, 1891
    - M.C. Ansbro & Co., 1901-1905
    - J.S. Armstrong, 1883
    - R.S. Atkins, 1903-1905
    - S.W. Backus (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Henry E. Baker, 1868-1873
    - Don Juan Bandini, 1886
    - Bandon Woolen Mills, 1895
    - William Bannon & Co., 1893-1894
    - Barnes and Horan, 1878
    - C.L. Barrington, 1894
    - Earl Bartlett, 1877-1885
    - H.S. Bates, 1897-1899
    - J.W. Belden, 1889
    - W.H. Bell, 1869
    - P.W. Bellingall, 1904
    - H.M. Black, 1888-1896
    - J.W. Bourdette and H.L. Billson, 1908
    - A.I. Bowie, 1867-1869
    - M.V. Brady, 1911
    - C.K. Breeze, 1887
    - G. Brignardello, 1875-1880 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - British Columbia, Bank of, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. Hannah Brosnan, 1891
    - Isidore Burns, 1895
    - W.J. Burns and N.W. Halsey, 1908
    - S.B. Burr (-vs-W.K. Durbrow), 1901
    - C.H. Burt, 1904
    - P.F. Butler, 1903-1907
    - J. Byrne & Co., 1902
    - Cain & Co., 1891 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - J. Caire, 1887-1891
    - California, Bank of, 1898-1899
    - California Furniture Co., 1890-1900 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - California Hat Co., 1903-1904
    - California Insurance Co., 1884
    - California Manganese Co., 1865
    - California Safe Deposit and Trust Co., 1910
    - California Wine Growers Union, 1894
    - J. Campbell, 1885
    - William Campbell, 1881
    - Lizzie M. Carroll, 1893
    - Mary A. Carroll, 1905-1909
    - John C. Carrole, 1870
    - Mary T. Carson, 1872
    - F.M. Cartan, 1889
    - Central Hardware and Supply Co., 1895-1903
    - F.R. Chamberlain, 1884
    - Mrs. Heloise Chamberlain, 1886-1898
    - John Chietovich, 1891-1893
    - George Chismore, 1898-1900
    - City Paving Co., 1871-1873
    - Clabrough and Golcher, 1885
    - I.M. Clark, 1889
    - W.S. Clark Estate, 1899-1900
    - Clauchï¿½ and Bon, 1895-1897
    - Andrew C. Coddington, 1876
    - William T. Coleman & Co., 1884
    - Comptoir National D'Escompte de Paris, 1889-1896 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Connelly and Borle, 1890
    - John Conner, 1883
    - John F. Conroy, 1879
    - Ferdinand Cortes, 1873-1876
    - R.W. Coulter, 1888-1900
    - Crandall Bros., 1889
    - C.G. Crawford & Co., 1876
    - Crescent Feather Co. Inc., 1908-1910
    - Day, (J.D., J.L., U.G.), 1903
    - J.J. Crofton, 1901
    - M.G. Cunningham, 1894
    - C. Curtin, 1901
    - S.S. Curtiss, 1904-1906
    - Daly Bros., 1901-1905 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Daly and Hawkins, 1879-1880
    - F. Daneri & Co., 1885
    - E.P. Danforth & Co., 1878
    - David Manufacturing Co., 1910-1911
    - Elizia Davis, 1894
    - Decker, Jewett, & Co. Bank, 1889
    - M.J. Dehon, 1868-1869
    - J.H. Denman, 1899
    - E. Dent, 1887
    - J. Dermody, 1893
    - I. Devine, 1883
    - Diepenbrock & Co., 1889
    - B.F. Dillingham, 1902-1911 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - R. Dinsmore & Co., 1882
    - J.W. Dolan, 1882-1883
    - Peter Donahue, 1873-1898
    - Daniel Donovan, 1898
    - Henry Doyle & Co., 1879-1904 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Henry Doyle & Co., 1905-1909 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Dunham, Carrigan & Hayden, 1890-1910 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Dwyer & Cartan, 1880
    - J.B. Dyer, 1887-1891
    - J.G. Eastland, 1887-1897 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Easton & Eldridge, 1883
    - Mary E. Edmonston, 1887
    - Edwards Publishing Co., 1896
    - Edwards & Co., 1890-1892
    - J.E. Ellis, 1879
    - Henry F. Emeric, 1891
    - J.J. Evans, 1893
    - Fannin & Franks, 1897-1904 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - L.Z. Farwell, 1878
    - P.G. Fay, 1879
    - Martin Feinall, 1890
    - Ferguson (Elijah, John, Ephraium, Alfred, James) and Merced Quartz Mining Co., 1861-1871
    - A.W. Fink, 1900-1901
    - R. Finke's widow, 1887
    - First National Bank-Albany, Oregon, 1888-1893
    - First National Bank-Portland, Oregon, 1886-1893
    - First National Bank-San Francisco, 1893-1895
    - Henry Fisher, 1871
    - I.H. Flickinger, 1885
    - George W. Flood, 1891
    - John W. Flood, 1896
    - A. Fodera Co., 1905
    - Mrs. Virginia Ford, 1894-1895
    - Francis & Valentine, 1875-1889
    - Frazer & Co., 1907-1908
    - Bernard Gallagher, 1881-1882 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Gallagher Bros., 1897-1900
    - P.G. Galpin, 1891-1908
    - Alexander Gamble, 1865-1873
    - Frank Garcia, 1900-1909
    - J.P. Garvey, 1881-1885
    - August Gast Bank Note and Lithographing Co., 1888
    - M. Gately, 1878
    - E. Gauthier, 1894
    - Dominick Gaven, 1865-1868
    - F.A. Geier, 1893-1900
    - German Savings & Loan Society, 1888
    - C.M. & Helen Garrish, 1903-1909 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - E.B. Gethin, 1878-1882
    - J.J. Gildea, 1899-1904
    - Mrs. Mary Glynn, 1894
    - Golden Gate Consolidated Hydraulic Mining Co., 1878
    - J.H. Goodman & Co., 1885
    - Robert & Amanda Goodwin, 1878-1879
    - Goodyear Rubber Co., 1898
    - Elizabeth Ann Gordon, 1870-1871
    - Charles Gotze, 1867
    - J.W. Grace & Co., 1885
    - J.G. Grannis & Co., 1903-1904
    - Julia H. Grady, 1881-1882
    - E.P. Gray, 1896
    - Adam I. Green, 1895
    - L. Greenbaum
    - Emma E. Gregson, 1891
    - H. Guernsey, 1897
    - Gunn & McMullin, 1892
    - John Hadsell, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Anais Hale, 1902
    - J. Hall
    - Hall's Safe and Lock Co., 1892-1893
    - Hallgarten & Co., 1879
    - M.F. and Aaron Hamburger, 1909
    - Hanley & Snow, 1877
    - William Hardiman, 1886-1888
    - J.T. Harlan, 1904
    - A.D. Harpold, 1898-1904
    - L. Hart & Son, 1900-1902
    - John Hastings, 1891
    - Hatch & Barclay, 1881-1884 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Havens & Co., 1879
    - Eli Hawkins, 1871
    - Sarah Haynes, 1909
    - John L. Heald, 1889-1890
    - Heath Mining Co., 1885
    - William Helbing, 1904-1906
    - August Hemme (Hemme & Long Piano Manufacturing), 1875-1877 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Hemme, 1878-August 1880 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Hemme, Sept 1880-1888 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Henderson Banking Co., 1882-1906 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Hendricks & Eakin
    - Richard Henry, Jr., 1884-1888
    - Herriman & Mills, 1891
    - J. Herzberg, 1888
    - J.L. Hicks, 1892-1900
    - F.A. Hihn, 1887-1907
    - Hilbert Bros., 1894-1901
    - John R. Hite, 1884-1907 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Walter Hoge, 1889
    - P. Holland, 1892
    - Holme & Nathan, 1907
    - M.F. Honan, 1884
    - Hops shipments, 1883-1884
    - Horn & Chapman, 1884
    - B.J. Horn & Sons, 1903-1904
    - Dexter Horton & Co., 1881
    - Edward Hull, 1887
    - M. Keating, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Daniel Keefe, 1902
    - B.R. Keith, 1895-1900
    - Kelleher & Browne, 1903-1905
    - G.W. Kellogg Co., 1899
    - Alfred R. Kelly, 1888-1889
    - Edward Kelly, 1887
    - Francis X. Kelly, 1866
    - M.L. Kelly, 1891-1894
    - Phillip Kennedy & Co.
    - Kennedy, Brennan & Co., 1881
    - Keystone Quartz Mining Co., 1869-1874
    - King County, Bank of, 1890
    - John Klein Electric Co., 1892-1906
    - Kohler & Chase, 1886-1899
    - Kohler & Frohling, 1888
    - Kolb & Denhard, 1890-1896
    - Ladies Silk Culture Society of California, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Lane & Connelly, 1890
    - Lang-Bleakmore, 1901
    - J.B. Lanny, 1882
    - Larkins & Co., 1896
    - J.P. Lartigan, 1901
    - Las Pasas Vineyard Co., 1893
    - L.R. Larzelere & Co., 1895
    - E. Lem, 1897
    - Mrs. Mary J. Lemman, 1899-1902
    - Joseph Levy, 1904-1907
    - John F. Lewis, 1872
    - E.W. Lick, 1907
    - E.R. Lillis, 1900
    - London, Paris & American Bank, 1887-1893
    - London & San Francisco Bank, Ltd., 1881
    - A.W. Louderback & Co., 1891
    - Lowenstein Bros., 1893
    - Otto Lhun & Co., 1891-1902
    - K.A. Lundstrom, 1892-1893
    - Lynde & Hough, 1888-1900
    - Charles Lyons, 1900
    - M.J. Lyon, 1884-1894
    - Mammoth Mining Co., 1880 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Marine Construction Co., 1904
    - Mariposa: Correspondence, 1871-1878 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Mariposa: Correspondence, 1879-1885 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Mariposa: Indentures, deeds, agreements, 1867-1872 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Mariposa: Legal disputes, 1867-1879 (Box 32)
    - Mariposa: Legal disputes, 1880-1881 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Mariposa: Legal disputes, 1882-1885 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Mariposa: Insurance policies (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Mariposa: Statements, financial reports, 1871-1877 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Mariposa: Statements, financial reports, 1879-1884 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Receipts, invoices, bills
    - Market Street Bank, 1882-1888 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Market Street Railway Co., 1902
    - Mrs. Lillie E. Marquett, 1888
    - Marshall & Reimers, 1897-1903
    - Martin Bros., 1906
    - S. Martin, 1894
    - J. Martenstein & Co., 1886-1897
    - Atkins Massey, 1889
    - D.J. Mercer, 1900
    - Charles Meinecke, 1900
    - Metten & Gebhardt, 1900
    - John or George Middleton, 1871-1877
    - Mildred Island Commercial Co., 1906 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Monarch Shoe Co., 1900
    - Moore, 1895
    - Moran & Co., 1895
    - Moynihan & Aitken, 1884-1885
    - Merchants National Bank of Tacoma
    - William Miller, 1880
    - Moller & McMullin, 1890-1892
    - Montealegre & Co., 1878
    - Francis Mora, 1886
    - Morgan & Chick, 1895
    - J.M. Moss, 1877-1880
    - E. Moulton, 1890
    - Muhr & Muhr, 1901
    - A. Muhs, 1898-1903
    - Muller-Byrne Co., 1901-1902
    - J.J. Mundwyler, 1900
    - B.D. Murphy, 1896-1899
    - Daniel T. Murphy, 1886-1887
    - Eugene P. Murphy, 1879-1881
    - Murphy Grant & Co., 1890
    - Mutual Biscuit Co., 1909 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - McAleer Mine, 1867-1872 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - McAlester, 1890-1891 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - McAlester check stubs, 1890-1891 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - A. McAlister (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - James McClosky, 1897 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Alicia McCone, 1908
    - J.W. McDonald, 1889-1901
    - John McEwen, 1871
    - Thomas McInerney, 1882-1886
    - McKay, 1892
    - John McKinnon, 1891-1896
    - Jane McLaughlin, 1876
    - Daniel McLeod, 1898-1903
    - McNally & Hawkins, 1878-1886
    - L.H. McRoskey, 1901
    - Nagle & Nagle, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Allison Neff, 1896-1900
    - Nevada Bank of San Francisco 1881-1890
    - Nevada Land and Mining Co. (Washoe United Consolidated Gold & Silver Mining Co.), 1864-1870 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Oakland Gas, Light & Heat Co., 1886 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Oberdeener, 1897-1905
    - P.T. O'Brien, 1902
    - Lillie O'Connor, 1885-1887
    - Moses, Elizia O'Connor, 1879-1893
    - Thomas O'Connor (Conroy & O'Connor), 1864-1891
    - Daniel O'Day, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Cornelius P. O'Donnell, 1881
    - John O'Kane, 1902-1903
    - B.P. Oliver, 1881-1904
    - Olson & Sonnenberg, 1908
    - Mary O'Meara, 1883
    - Omnibus Cable Co., 1890-1895
    - Neil O'Neill, 1904
    - Oregon, Bank of, 1889-1894
    - Owens Lake Borax Mining & Manufacturing Co., 1901
    - Pacific Bank, 1888-1890 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Pacific Gas Engine Co., 1891
    - Pacific Lumber Co., 1897
    - Pacific Packing & Navigation Co., 1902
    - Pacific Surety Co., 1893-1908
    - Pacific Wireless Telegraph, 1905-1910
    - John Packard, 1863
    - Pajaro Fruit & Land Co., 1900-1902
    - Palace Hotel, 1881
    - P.P. Parrott, 1885
    - Payne, 1909
    - People's Home Savings Bank, 1889-1893
    - William M. Pierson, 1897-1900
    - Pinole, Bank of, 1906
    - Pioneer Woolen Factory, 1884
    - G.B. Polhemus, 1900-1903
    - Preston & McKinnon, 1895-1901
    - Provo Woolen Mills Co., 1896
    - Railroad Syndicate subscription, 1892 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - C.T. Reed, 1882
    - Rehfisch & Co., 1886
    - Refugio Mining Co., 1863
    - P.F. Reilly, 1891-1901
    - Ben Richardson, 1879-1880
    - A.E. Brooke Ridley, 1899-1900
    - T.P. Riordan, 1886-1902
    - W.H. Rose, 1884
    - W.S. Rosecrans, 1878
    - Rosedale Raisin Vineyard, 1890
    - A.M. Rutherford, 1888
    - St. Ignatius College, San Francisco, 1897 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - St. Joseph's School, Menlo Park, 1906
    - Salinas City Bank, 1891
    - Sanborn Map & Publishing Co., 1888
    - San Francisco Gas & Electric, 1907
    - San Francisco Undertaking Co., 1891
    - San Joaquin Lumber Co., 1893
    - San Jose Safe Deposit Bank, 1885-1906
    - Banking House of Sather & Co., 1886-1892
    - Jacob Saunders, 1900-1904
    - Schulz & Ruckgaber, 1886-1893
    - Bank of Scio, 1890
    - Angela R. Scott, 1901-1906 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Scottish Union & National Insurance Co. of Edinburgh, 1881
    - S.H. Seymour, 1886
    - John Shawhan, 1878-1888
    - Daniel Sheerin & Sons, 1893-1899
    - George A. Sheppard, 1891-1901
    - A. Schilling & Co., 1899
    - L. Schilling, 1906
    - Shasta Lumber Co., 1893
    - George W. Sherve, 1888-1894
    - Sierra Nevada Mining stock, 1907-1908
    - Siller Bros., 1905
    - Peter Simmons & Co., 1882
    - J. Sinclair, 1891-1899
    - Singer Manufacturing Co., 1887-1899
    - Sisson, Crocker & Co., 1892
    - A.F. Snowball, 1890
    - C. Solomon, Jr., 1901
    - South Prairie Coal Co., 1902
    - E.B.D. Spagnoli, 1908
    - Heinz Springe, 1907-1908 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Alice Stafford, 1909
    - State National Bank, 1879
    - Stauffer Chemical Co., 1895-1899
    - E.A. Stent, 1898-1899
    - Stockton Gas & Electric, 1896-1902
    - Vanderlynn Stow, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - W.E. Straut & Co., 1888
    - Mrs. Ellen M. Stuart, 1896
    - Sullivan, Kelly & Co., 1888
    - Francis Sullivan, 1885
    - Frank J. Symmons, 1894
    - Tallant & Co., 1888-1891 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - J.S. Thomas, 1909
    - James A. Thompson, 1887-1899 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Thorpe, 1878-1881 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Louis Thors, 1887
    - Susanna M. Throckmorton, 1896
    - H.N. Tilden, 1881-1905
    - Tobin & Tobin, 1885-1888
    - Lemoine Tural & Co., 1884-1885
    - Mary E. Twing, 1884
    - John Twohig, 1891-1892
    - Union Brewing Co., 1902 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Union Insurance Co., 1880-1889
    - Union Iron Works, 1884
    - Union National Bank, 1881
    - Union Pulp & Paper Co., 1904
    - Union Superphosphate Co., 1907
    - Union Transfer Co., 1902-1904
    - United Workingmen's Boot & Shoe Manufacturing Co., 1888-1901
    - Upper San Joaquin Irrigating Co., 1879-1882
    - Van Frank Electric & Manufacturing Co., 1903-1906 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - (California) Vigorit Powder Co., 1901-1904
    - Wakefield Rattan Co., 1890 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - L.B. Wakefield & Co., 1881-1888
    - Judge Wallace, 1900
    - John B. Ward, 1887
    - Margaret Warde, 1889
    - Washington Grammar School, 1905-1907
    - F.G. Waterhouse, 1899 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - N.J. Weaver, 1891-1902
    - Ed Weil & Co., 1893
    - Weinstock, Lubin & Co., 1899
    - Wells, Fargo & Co., 1887-1893
    - Wempe Bros., 1905
    - Weniger & Bielenberg, 1902
    - F. Wensinger, 1880-1888
    - Westcott & Son, 1895 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Wheeland & Collins, 1904
    - George H. Whipple, 1901
    - White Bros., 1888
    - Jane T. White, 1890
    - Whitney Estate, 1909
    - George Whittell, 1867
    - H. Whittell, 1867
    - F. Whooten, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Witzel & Baker, 1895-1903
    - J. Wolfskill, 1880
    - Mrs. E.R. Wood, 1890
    - Jesse Woods, 1905
    - Wreden, Kohlmoos Co. (formerly Wolf, Wreden Co.), 1896-1905
    - G. Wrez, 1884
    - John T. Wright, 1909
    - York, Whitworth & Shurtleff
    - George H. Young, 1908
  - LETTERS OF CREDIT (numbered series) (Box 11)
    - 465-682
    - 866-931
  - INSURANCE POLICIES (arranged by insurance co.) (Box 12)
    - Pacific Coast Canning Co., 1907-1911
    - J.A. Donohoe Estate, 1906
    - Miscellaneous, 1881-1906
  - FINANCIAL BUSINESS PAPERS
    - Income tax returns & forms, 1863-Aug 1866 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Income tax returns & forms, Sept 1866-Dec 1868 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Income tax returns & forms, 1869-1873 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Income tax returns & forms, 1874-1878 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Income tax returns & forms, 1879-1883 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Income tax returns & forms, 1884-1894 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Semi-annual reports on bank's condition (to Board of Bank Commissioners), 1875-1890 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Semi-annual reports, 1891-1893 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Statements, March 1891-April 1893 (Box 14, Folder 70)
      - Balance sheets
      - Bills Receivable
    - Statements, May 1893-March 1898 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Bills to Donohoe, Kelly Banking Co. (A-L) (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Bills to Donohoe, Kelly Banking Co. (M-Y) (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Eastern & foreign telegrams, July 1880-June 1881 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Eastern & foreign telegrams, July 1881-June;882 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Eastern & foreign telegrams, July 1884-May 1885 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Eastern & foreign telegrams, June 1885-July 1886 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Cipher lists; two small bound cipher books, 1864-1867 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Coupons, stocks, bonds, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1872-1912 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - CHECK SAMPLES, ACCOUNT SAMPLES
    - Account envelopes (envelopes are empty, for the most part; deposits and payments on notes recorded on backs), 1908-1914 (Box 16)
    - Statements of other banks, Dec 1916 (Box 17, Folder 81)
      - a.Comptoir National d'Escompte De Paris
      - b.Federal Reserve Bank, (Dec 1917)
      - c.Hibernian Banking Association, Chicago
      - d.Bank of Ireland
      - e.Mechanics-American National Bank, St. Louis
      - f.National Bank of O.D. Mills & Co., Sacramento
      - g.National Shawmut Bank, Boston
      - h.Bank of New York
      - i.Parr's Bank Ltd., London
    - Collection notices (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Exchange tags, deposit slips (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Clearing House checks, memos, proofs (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Check samples, used (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Check samples, unused (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Samples of Letters of Credit (Box 17, Folder 87)
      - Letter of Indication
      - Booklets regarding travel
      - Travelers' Checques
      - Cable Code
    - Paying Teller's cash & balance sheets (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Report by Clearing House Examiner, 1908 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- Series B. General Account Books
  - Daybook, Dec 1906-Nov 1907 (Volume 18)
  - Daybook, Nov 1907-Dec 1907 (Volume 19)
  - Daybook, Dec 1907-July 1908 (Volume 20)
  - Daybook (Hibernian Banking Association), Dec 1894-Dec 1899 (Volume 21)
  - Daybook (Hibernian), Jan 1900-Aug 1906 (Volume 22)
  - Daybook (Bank of New York), March 1894-July 1896 (Volume 23)
  - Daybook (Bank of New York), July 1896-Jan 1901 (Volume 24)
  - Daybook, Jan 1901-Aug 1906 (Volume 25)
  - Daybook (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), May 1906-July 1906 (Volume 26)
  - Daybook (B. of the M.Co.), Sept 1901-Aug 1906 (Volume 27)
  - Daybook (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), Nov 1899-March 1906 (Volume 28)